(Raj:)I can and I did.
Look up "dibs" in Wikipedia.
(Sheldon:)Dibs doesn't apply in a bidding war.
(Leonard:)It's not a bidding war. I'm selling it all
to Larry down at the comic-book store.
- Why Larry? Did Larry call dibs?
- Will you forget dibs?
(Leonard:)He offered me a fair price
for the whole collection.
- What's the number? I'll match it.
- I'll match it, plus 1000 rupees.
- What's the exchange rate?
- None of your business. Take it or leave it.
Mom, my bar mitzvah bonds,
how much do I got?
Thanks. I can go $2600
and two trees in Israel.
(Leonard:)Forget it. Guys, if I sell to one of you,
the other two are gonna be mad at me.
Who cares? As long as you pick me.
(Raj:)Okay, Leonard, put down the box.
Let's talk.
(Leonard:)Sorry, Raj, my mind is made up.
(Sheldon(moving to block his path):)No. I can't let you do this.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, get out of my way.
(Sheldon(brandishing toy sword from Leonard's box):)None shall pass.
(Penny:)Okay.